# Dhanu Satrio Darjanto

Bekasi 17116 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhanu-satrio-175775208 | 081298063349 | satriodhanu12@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am currently a third-year informatics student, future mobile application developer. I am very interested in the world of technology, especially in a mobile applications. My passion for mobile application brought me to Telkom University. For the last 3 years, I studied many programming languages such as Python, Golang, and C++ to improve my problem-solving skill. Now I am currently being active as a practice assistant in Computer Network and Operating System course, being a lecturer assistant is an honor because it will improve my experience, time management skills, and discipline.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Telkom University

Mathematic Discrete Asistant Lecturer

(June 2022 - September 2022)

- Conducting task evaluation and summarization.
- Performing testing on online quiz questions.
- Assisting and answering student questions on an online forum.

Practice Assistant for Computer Network

(March 2023 - June 2023)

- Conducting assessments on laboratory journals.
- Explaining laboratory materials.
- Providing assistance to students during major assignments.

Practice Assistant for Operating System

(March 2023 - June 2023)

- Conducting assessments on laboratory journals.
- Explaining laboratory materials.
- Providing assistance to students during major assignments.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Telkom University**

(September 2020 - June 2023)

3.95

- **Bachelors** Bachelor Degree in Informatics
- Participant at GEMASTIK XIV Competitive Programming (Aug 2021)
- Creating an alien invasion game in Python.
- Developing a Simple Learning Management System in Python.
- Building a program with Genetic Algorithm in Python

## SMAN 3 Bekasi

(July 2017 - July 2020)

High School Senior High School

The organizing committee of the SMAN 3 Bekasi's birthday event

### **SKILLS**

Teamwork, Time Management, Problem Solving, Programming, Analytical Skills, Math Skills, Python, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Golang.